RERATILWE RONNEL KEKANA

Psychologist

<u>0723150326</u>

reratilwek@gmail.com

in <u>reratilwe-kekana</u>

Pretoria Arcadia



An optimistic and motivated professional with Bachelor of Arts in Psychology, Criminology and Sociology and Bachelor of Social Sciences Honours Psychology graduate from the University of Pretoria. I have 1 year experience as an Analysis and Coordination intern for the SAPS Crime Intelligence, I possess the following skills communication, correspondence, risky analysis, research, collating of information and establishment of database including compilation of threat assessments. I have a passion for social issues and providing solutions.

I'm currently looking for a company with a healthy environment where my skills will be utilized to the betterment and growth of the company also of the industry and which will in turn give me an opportunity to learn

WORK EXPERIENCES

Analysis and Coordination Intern

South African Crime Intelligence | Aug 2019 - Aug 2020

- Compile threat assessments on focus area
- Enrich information to conduct strategic data analysis
- Compile departmental intelligence estimate on counter narcotics and gangsterism threat assessments
- Compile intelligence analysis reports related to analysis
- Compile profiles in relation to individuals, activities, organizations and events assessments
- Type official correspondence
- Database
- File/archive correspondence/reports received as well as open enquiry files

Mentor

Stars mentorship program, University of Pretoria | 2017 - 2018

The programme offers students assistance at the social and emotional levels with a view to enhancing their academic performance. As a mentor I was paired with a first-year student to assist and help them to adapt to the University life. As a mentor I provided the following:

- Guidance with regards to the various challenges
- Assistance in academic and personal problems
- Reference to competent people if necessary

Volunteer and Trainee

Center of Sexualities, Aids and Gender | 2017

The CSA&G uses an intersectional approach to working with constituents and broader issues of human rights and social justice, so that our work was to focus on people as complex bearers of multiple, contextual and fluid identities. The main focus was on:

- Gender-based justice
- An introduction to counselling
- HIV/AIDS and human rights education
- The challenges and dynamics of gender, identity, race and class

Psyche society student member

University of Pretoria | 2016

Psyche aims to provide students with safe volunteering opportunities to bridge the gap between the theoretical knowledge and practical experience in the field of Psychology. It also strives to bring mental health and mental health awareness to the student body through many on-campus activities.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Social Sciences Honours Psychology

University of Pretoria | 2018

Majors: Psychological assessment, Neuropsychology, Cognitive psychology, Psychopathology, Social Psychology, Theories and Paradigms, Research Methodology and Research Paper

BA HumanitiesUniversity of Pretoria | 2015 - 2017

Majors: Mathematics, Physical Science, Life Sciences, Geography, English

CERTIFICATES

The Fundamentals of Digital Marketing

Google Digital Skills for Africa (2021)

SKILLS

Computer skills

Proficient user of MS Word, Excel and Power point.

Communication & Writing skills

High level of communication skills both written and oral seen through projects

Presentations of reports and working effectively with groups

High level of communication skills both written and oral seen through projects

Research and report writing

Public Speaking

Admin skills

General office management, Organizational skills and Time management skills

Professional

Effective communication

Team player

Strong problem solver

Good time management

LANGUAGES

Sepedi (Native)

English (Professional)

INTERESTS

Music

Politics

Art & Fashion

Travelling